dividend.com 2005-11-21

# Scripophily .com - Old Stock Certificate Superstore - The Gift of History Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

[](https://www.truste.org/validate/361) At Scripophily.com we take your privacy very seriously. We keep everything strictly confidential. We do not share any personal information with any outside company including maillists, marketing or telemarketing services. If you have any questions or need any additional information feel free to call us 1-888-STOCKS or send us an email.

Your Privacy Assured

Your privacy is of great concern to Scripophily.com. We use the information you provide to process your order and to ensure that your experience on our site is as enjoyable and efficient as possible.

The Information We Gather and How We Use It

Our system automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on our Internet store. We do not use any of the navigational data that you - as an individual - provide while browsing or shopping on the Internet Store; nor do we share this data with anyone outside our company. We do use navigational information in the aggregate to understand how our visitors shop in our store so we can make Scripophily.com better. Our site also uses "cookies" so you can keep track of the items you have placed in your shopping bag. Each time you return to our Internet Store your shopping bag will be just as you left it. We may also use and store information you give us (e.g., your shipping or billing address) so you do not have to reenter it each time you visit. In order to fulfill your order and provide you with highest level of customer service, we must ask you for personal information. Scripophily.com collects your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information in order to deliver your order promptly and to the correct address. We use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation of your order. We will also send an e-mail when your package is shipped and include the shipper's tracking number. You may also choose to register with us. Registration provides advantages like faster check out; ability to store shipping addresses; advanced notification on upcoming promotions; and exclusive invitations to private sales and events. By registering, you can also update your personal information through your Scripophily.com account. If you place an order, registering allows you to track your order status, but is not required to complete the order process. Scripophily.com does not disclose, share, sell, or trade any personal or individual information that it collects to third parties, other than in the course of completing a transaction, providing you with information that you have requested, or in response to an investigation involving legal matters. While we may provide aggregate information regarding site usage to third parties, such as statistics on site traffic and sales, you can rest assured that we will only work with external companies who will respect our customer's privacy.

Safety and Privacy of Minors

Scripophily.com does not target children nor does Scripophily.com expect to attract children to its site. Because of this, our privacy measures have not been specifically developed for their protection on the Internet. We do ask that minors do not submit information to Scripophily.com without the express consent and participation of a parent or legal guardian.

Links

Occasionally, this site may contain links to other sites. Scripophily.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites. We suggest you check the privacy statement on each site that you visit.

Contacting the Website

If you have any questions or concerns about the Scripophily.com privacy policy, contact us at Scripophily@yahoo.com, call toll-free 1-888-STOCKS6 or 703-787-3552, or write to us at: Scripophily.com P.O. Box 223795 Chantilly, Virginia 20153

Secure Transactions

Statistically, it's safer to shop online with your credit card than to use it in a restaurant or department store. At Scripophily.com, protecting your personal information is extremely important to us. To ensure that you never have to worry about credit card safety when you shop in our store, we use security software called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. When you connect with our secure server, they exchange a handshake, which initiates a secure session. In most browsers, look for a key or lock icon to indicate that you are in the SSL mode. From that point on during your secure session, all the information sent between you and Scripophily.com is protected by SSL encryption.

Once we receive your credit card information, it is immediately encrypted and stored.. This step prevents anyone except the credit card authorization company from viewing it. To ensure your proper processing of your order, we will manually review each order prior to charging your credit card. We do this to so you know you are dealing with a person not a computer!

We will send you an immediate email verifying receipt of your order with your order confirmation number. Please keep this number handy if you need to contact us with any questions about your order.
